all right everybody hey
it's a Saturday normally I would go
bunch of different places we're just
going to do the goblin route Daily
Bridge
Goblin and we're in Davidson
so should be a lot of people out
today um I'm also not going to talk as
much today I'm going to go for more of
kind of an IRL Vibe just to enjoy it let
you guys hear it because there's a lot
of people out maybe we could save the
talking for the the streams where
um there's something to talk about and
it's pretty boring out or something it's
overcast how you doing C so come on in
say hi if you have questions let me know
otherwise I'm just going to be breathing
I'm also trying a different audio thing
I've got the ASMR audio set up on today
that's a left and right stereo so this
should be your
left this should be
right if it's not if that's not left and
that's not right please tell me right
away and and here we
[Music]
go this
very saky today
[Music]
heart rate's uh janky today as
well uh the reason for that is
because my I ran out of battery and then
I tried to take a battery up and my $120
garment is actually
broken because the place put the battery
in
is it kind of fails pretty
easily so
it's kind of sad to
hear so yeah I have a like a $50 one
that has a buil-in 3 and a half year
battery and it's totally
fine
so I'm going be using that instead
reason chat is having trouble
today why
it's such great weather
ouch
what's going
on hey there's the hockey
SK
actually hey how are
you you don't know with my Wi-Fi I
cannot figure it out
looks like it's
is acting up for some reason do not know
why maybe the
vibration tank hits in
now now could be it I don't know might
have to talk through some of the battery
connectors to
yeah I still can't see you guys' chat
chatting at me
but come around
eventually this is real time IRL app is
kind of
janky honestly it's got It's got
problems somebody made it for free know
so probably change chat monitoring
apps I notic this one does not recover
from switches from internet very well
not like the other ones
anyway yeah it's like making me resign
into twitch
now which is tot
stupid yeah now it's frozen
it's silly Frozen this
app sh out I might ttch app today
probably should use it anyway the Twitch
app has gotten a lot better I think the
built-in Twitch
app hey Amazon Prime there's number one
let's count them
today Amazon Prime truck number
one all right I'm going back to Twitch
for monitoring able to read your
[Music]
chat going to BL to you guys
now
um all right we got it's back I'm
watching I'm using the Twitch app this
time unfortunately that means I won't
have streight
stickers so you guys can hear me though
yeah almost killed by an Amazon Prime
truck going
backwards yet by Amazon Prime
so wait a second are you
guys not hearing
me I me imagine
it this one
is these are all things that are really
hard to
validate without being able to talk to
you
no that app is still
bork streamer is upline
oh Logistics Logistics
Logistics are you guys there
are you guys
there God even the Twitch app won't work
now what the is going
on streamer Veil
I have no
idea um this isn't connected to the
internet it says the mini mini says it
doesn't have any Internet
available let's
try all right there we go let's try this
now okay there now it came through for
some
reason on the bridge okay so I can
that's
weird yeah
three
viewers we went from 8 to three just cuz
I'm around so can you guys not
see
anything I mean what's going on I need
to I need to see if you are here
[Music]
it say there's
eight I'm just going to keep moving cuz
I can't that's one thing I can't do is I
cannot
let all right so for some reason now we
have access now we have Internet okay
now I can see the preview thank
god
um huh
I decided to uh leave the camera pointed
kind of naturally down a little bit more
today
so is there sound that's what I want to
know is there sound yes or
no looks
like answer that question for me yet
so is there
sound yeah the bike it's the same bike
as before I need to change I think you
for the reminder
for
h
there is
sound okay
Punchy little Hill
my three
sisters I call
them try not to overwhelm you guys with
my hard heavy
breathing but I'm
tired for
these are good
nice I I guys let me know how the mics
are working out
because I put them on my
boobies it's funny I have like two puff
balls right where my nipples are
and I put a left one on and a right one
on and I pointed it to the left and to
the
right
so happy to have any feedbook about
about
audio you want to provide
here oh there's no traffic is is
Saturday it's awesome
he's been fantastic
today cleaning house literally doing
laundry we decided to take Saturday off
of
yoga that's the normal tradition Vera
anyway
so I didn't keep doing it though but
this
little you know it's good for
him world
I noticed that the angle on my camera
was a little bit too far up and it
didn't
match what I'm normally used to seeing
when I ride my bike and I put a video up
on YouTube
today uh of the bike ride and I
figured if people want to put it on to
watch while they're doing indoor
writing I needed to point it down a
little bit more to make make it more
realistic so they can see the road
passing them
by it's not as visually interesting but
it's more
realistic my video yesterday looked like
I always had my head tilted up all the
time you know I kept while I was
watching the video I kept tilting my
head up because I was getting immersed
in the video and I was like come on I
just need to look up a or look down a
little more that was it
no heart rate monitor today it
died new heart rate monitor coming
tomorrow or actually today by
5 got the $45
one with a 3E
battery so hopefully that'll be
good oh burgers are
awesome went home had a huge smoothie
took a
nap had had one of my wife's grap
Burgers the next day and when she got
there we
watched couple couple shows and went to
bed
very
routine really love it actually
saw all these people on
straa going on their bike rides and
I two or three of them went
on it's a route they call the oo
here and it goes completely most of the
road is on
which is like completely
dangerous that just blows me away how
many cyclists insist on that route I
can't quite figure it
out there's no reason to put you in
yourself in
danger many
naps I took an out one today took a I
set the timer for 30 minutes but it ends
up being about a 20-minute nap usually
I do two or three a
[Music]
day I usually put them right before like
a session like I'll take a break or
something got to be careful
because if you take if you do it
and you eat something hard to digest you
end up getting in digestion so
don't recommend that but if you have
something liquid
or there something called a coffee nap
people do sometimes I don't do it but
they'll drink coffee and then take a nap
and by the time the 20 or 30 minutes is
over the caffeine is kicked
in caffeine takes about 30 minutes to
register to your system you don't get
the hit from caffeine right away you
have to
wait that's one of the reasons that
putting caffeine in
[Applause]
your water bottles bad idea unless you
know you're going for a really long time
these caffeine jails are a total
joke because they don't that B12 will bu
B12 hits you right away soon as it the
caffeine doesn't caffeine has to be
digested and a different way
apparently
and so the idea of a coffee nap is since
it takes you never ever want to take a
nap more than 20 minutes 30 minutes tops
because then you hit R State and you
start getting really groggy your your
body releases a chemical to paralyze you
that's What Makes You groggy it's also
what Sleep Walkers don't
have their bodies fail to release the
chemical that paralyzes
them the paralyzation is also the reason
everybody thinks to have a demon on
their chest when they partially wake up
and they're filled with that paralyzing
chemical still and they can't
move so your body I don't know the name
of it but I I just know that
your your your body your body paralyzes
you so you don't walk around when you're
asleep while you're
dreaming and that's why you're always
like walking in mud and stuff like
that and people who Sleepwalk don't have
that I sometimes do put coffee in my
smoothies but again it's only if I'm
looking to to power up for something
that's coming like in 40 minutes the
fastest caffeine hits my system is about
40 minutes
away
so if you drink your coffee
slow you know by the time you're
finished with your coffee if you're
having a nice coffee talk with your wife
in the morning like today
then
yeah so the idea of a cat of a coffee
nap is like when you need to get
re-energized for the day like in the
afternoon if you're a tech worker you
need your brain to
work taking a nap is the single best way
to get your brain to work
again um taking a 90-minute nap doing a
full R cycle that's the best way but not
everybody can do that obviously and you
have to get that just right by the way
cuz if you do it too long it's really
hard to do because everybody's first Ram
cycle is different I've actually tracked
mine my Ram cycle is short than medium
then long through the through like an 8
Hour night I have like three Rim
Cycles
anyway interesting
stuff
Gaba
yeah but you don't you don't want any of
that chemical in your system if you're
trying to take a nap and to wake you up
to get more energy
so there's a shallow sleep cycle that
happens right before Ram
State
and I mean everybody here knows it it's
that it's that amount of sleep that you
wake up and it feels like you've been
sleeping for 3 hours but you really
haven't you only slept for like 10 15
minutes I used to have that all the time
in school I like fall asleep on the desk
and wake up and thought I was there for
6 hours
I've also noticed if I have a really
scary loud
alarm that when I wake up it injects me
with adrenaline on top of the
rest because they
like cuz there's a SC scary alarm right
so I do that on
purpose I'm making my alarm scary on
purpose because I don't want one of
these nice peaceful alarms I want an
alarm that's going to inject my body
with adrenaline when I wake up
so I get this hit of adrenaline right
away and then I'm like up right my heart
super supercharged my body got some
rest the caffeine has had 30 minutes to
kick in so it's about to kick
in and
then you're good to go and if you if
you've done your B12 during the
day that just that's how I that's how I
control my my energy how I stay
energetic oh was have just kind of fade
away especially afterno for me after
you've had a big meal or something I try
not to have big meals during the day
because they Tire me out but even a big
smoothie one of the biggest mistakes I
ever made
was
doing a big bowl of guacamole and you
know like a handful of chips corn chips
and then going right to
sleep I woke up just G it was
horrible cuz I couldn't digest any of it
just sat in my stomach the time I was
napping you got to make sure the food
you
eat about an hour before you take a nap
is
really either already digested
or on its way to being digested can't be
in your stomach still a lot of it
anyway that's why liquid
liquid meals like smoothies and stuff
are so good during the
day because they don't tax your body
your body doesn't have to work to do any
digestion at all it just absorbs
everything best shape I ever been in my
life the whole day was all
liquid add like two or three smoothies a
day different kinds of
smoothies I had to eventually start
eating more
people think oh hey it's a liquid diet
you're not getting any fiber
Boney you actually
are especially if you're putting
cucumber
celery
apples spinach it's all natural fiber
it's a good fiber soluble
fiber insoluble fiber sorry soluble
fibers that sort
of pasty stuff that comes out of
oatmeal which everybody say is really
good for your digestive tract might be
true but
it's it does a different thing to you
for
sure affects your body for sure
differently not a fan of oatmeal
anymore it really is just just learn it
just doesn't digest very
well
period like a a big a big breakfast of
oatmeal is one of the worst things you
could do for
me because it's it doesn't digest it
just hangs around my body woke up it's
like hey I want
nutrients and the oatmeal shuts it all
down says nope can't have any nutrients
you got to deal with this fiber I don't
like it that's why breakfast smoothies
are so popular with high with endurance
athletes and
everybody because it gives them all
their micronutrients and their
macronutrients loads up their carb blood
sugar
you know nice digestible eggs unfried
eggs giv see some good
protein gives your stomach something to
hold on to for like 3 four five hours
and if you have like a liquid
lunch that'll get you
through until you're going to go to your
ride then you can carve up and do your
ride and come back and have a big old
meal that's going to put you to
sleep like a biver or something
and that that but that meal will be your
the meal your body uses to rebuild
everything I read another thing that
said that your body will adapt what it
does during your during your sleep cycle
the Bas on what nutrients are in your
system and that most protein should
be taken if you want to protein you want
to take protein to rebuild your body one
of the things is to put to take high
diges of protein about an hour before
you go to bed and then your your stomach
will be full of protein good protein
digestible protein not you know a steak
or something
and because you don't want the
indigestion from
that and then your body will will be
triggered to rebuild when you sleep more
than usual because it's like damn I got
all this protein I should probably use
it and it rebuilds I've noticed that
when I do that I wake up and my
fingernails are
longer you know things like that the
small things help you know that your
system is working one of the best
indicators of your system working for me
honest to God is how fast my hair grows
and I'm because I'm bald and how fast my
fingernails grow because those are based
on protein
syns and I've noticed that when I'm
having when I have a really good build
cycle and I wake up and I feel like
ready to take on the world that I
usually will start to have longer
fingernails faster that's I know my
system's
working it's almost like the rings of a
tree
right you can tell when the tree is
distressed versus when it's not you can
actually look if you look at a hair
follicle people do this right you can
look at a hair follicle on the
microscope and you can tell when people
have been nutrient deficient and stuff
just by looking at the hair follicle
I'm not even looking at my heart
rate hey Chi Chin
chong
chuch some of these names CU I
swear I I put
protein in a smoothie but I don't do
that
until I
do I have done protein
smoothies either at
lunchtime I'll do like a banana peanut
butter and chocolate
smoothie that's actually my my favorite
treat like when I'm like really craving
a milkshake or something
one of my favorite things is to get a is
to get one of
those because they are so good they
they're they're they taste just like
they're so decadent you
know just a couple scoops of chocolate
protein or if you use vanilla protein
and just put like oval teen in it
chocolate
flavor and you just put like a
tablespoon of peanut butter and half a
banana if I put I sometimes put a whole
banana but bananas are kind of bananas
can kind of mess you up what is that
going
on I got to go I got to know there's
some kind of event going on down there I
got to go check it out I'm just too
curious not to check it
out I don't know what's going
on oh
D oh a wedding it is a
[Music]
wedding a
wedding that's kind of cool getting
married on the golf
course
yeah all rest up all these rich golf
country called people
CR yeah the pool's closed down
H that's
lot I think I think everything did close
out you know what I think was it Labor
Day I think Labor Day is when everything
shuts down that's also when all the
water goes off
the water fountains and stuff
I got some of
my straa local Legend back we're doing
the same route every
day if you don't know straa
is place where people go brag about what
they do
I don't so much I just like the tracking
on
it history and
stuff
but one of the things I do
like I mean I'm I'm on a very slow bike
here
so you
know there are people that like take
King of the Hill segments which means
they the fastest on a
segment yeah
and they will
uh they'll do it at night when there's
no traic or anything on their fastest
possible like on their tra bike or
something I'm like nope but there's
another thing you can do called local
Legend and it means you basically own
the
segment because you do the segment more
than anyone else so your bragging rights
is like oh you're the fastest on the
segment one time in like 19
74 pretending like straa existed back
then good for you as for
me I do I I do a you know hey Amazon
Prime
again I do a decent time on this segment
every day get in get behind me
hold my
beer I really like it I like it I love I
love the local budget thing I mean if
you're going to brag BR about how
consistent your training
is not how much you can you know how
fast you can go on one special day and
how fast your gear is how consistent are
you in your
training you know I mean seriously if
you're going to flex about being an
athlete on
straa which you know some type of flex
some people go there for support some
people go there just for number tracking
I kind of go for all that but mostly the
tracking part it it's kind of fun to
meet new people I really like when you
pass somebody you can look them up later
on
flyby and kind of get to know them
that's kind of cool I do like meeting
people that like to
bike
so yeah but if when it comes to local
edging I mean if you're going to flex
the whole point of the whole point of
flexing on straa is to say look at how
fast I am for sure but more than that is
look at how Comm I am to the
lifestyle you
know I think I I I respect the people
that are the local Legends way more than
I respect the fast
people because these are people that
have made cycling a part of their lives
some of them bike commute every
day some of
them you
know yeah heart rate's
wrong heart my heart might monitor is
broken I'm not I don't have it on today
sorry it's it's it's locked down from
yeah I just climbed that hill at a 104
heart rate I'm a
Superman
no my the battery was dying and then I
took it apart and then it completely
collapsed it's all rotted out and
everything yeah it was like a $140 heart
rate
monitor I mean heart rate strap
compared to the $50 one that you never
have to open up guess what one I
bought I mean seriously think about this
for a second what is the benefit of the
high-end $130 heart rate monitor there's
a NE better
one this the same
data absolutely same data
so you can you can pay like I don't know
let's say 150 right 150 for mot you have
to change your battery all the time it
rots and goes
bad or you can pay $45 every 3
years do the
math so for the same price as the Fancy
Fancy Fancy Fancy gar garment heart REM
monitor with like the the little ring on
it and everything so everybody knows
you're wearing a garment heart REM
monitor you can show off totally
stupid
but for the same price of that you can
buy three maybe four of the cheaper R
monitors that do the exactly the same
thing they have a built-in battery and
are black
I don't know about
that there is no heart r on there is
only
Zool I just think it's funny remember
that part where I said I wasn't going to
talk yeah that didn't last very
God I love my little route it's just so
much it's so fun especially on Saturday
Sunday it's just so peaceful and
happy yeah 198 is my
Max actually
178 I think is my Max he say one it used
to be my
Max I was a kid
max heart rate goes down substantially
when
you
probably is there game over here I mean
we'll have to go check it out at the
end where they're probably doing an
activity of some kind cuz this is like
prime time to be out doing something
right looking forward to doing another
Charlotte Charlotte ride this
Friday we're going to do mean all kinds
of cycling this
Friday the gravel back ride to shout and
then on the
way and then we'll be doing critical
mass I'm going to meet up with
Doris this coming
Friday if you like IRL content on the
bike POV that's going to be a good
day they lots and lots to see on there
people watching
and stuff
reminds me I need to buy a little us
teeny tiny USB charger brick for my
speakers I mean for my
mics and I can just have both mics on at
the same
time it's very
safe I mean I mean I think I'm here the
ultimate safety zone would probably be
the track they have a Vel
drum in South
Charlotte never been there we actually
met one last year we met a competitor
from New York I think who was competing
in a mill Drome race he was a track
cyclist he was a really nice guy I
actually he told me where it was I was
going to I was planing out meeting him
there I just never
went what up going
on my M and I talked about that again
today about
how people who have real
jobs don't have
time ambitious healthy people with real
jobs don't have a lot of extra
time and the minimum is an hour a day of
exercise
minimum and I mean if you count if
that's like 30 minutes of exercise you
know 30 minutes of changing and getting
your shower up and ready to go back to
work if if you do an honest st's work
has 8 hours a
day if you have a you have a an average
but if you have an average
commute that's an hour day 2 hours an
hour day hey look Crocs
spent a couple hours with your family
eating and talking about the
day no more time left that's it it's
right back when I was starting out as a
techie and a young
claer especially we got young kids man
then they push add up to 4 hours a
day with the
family when I back when I worked to
9 to teleport the only way I could even
get any exercise cuz there was a time
was to bike to
work and bike to work or i'
run I take a lunch
break to be completely honest I have
learned something I don't even know if I
want to say it out
loud the average person has four
productive hours of work a day according
to the science on
productivity think about that four
productive hours a day we're talking
about people who
commute that means 3 or 4 hours a day is
wasted just scoring around or walking to
meetings or like little you know
checking unnecessary email or getting
distracted or going to the bathroom or
grabbing a bite to
eat so the the The Logical takeaway from
that
is if you're if you're
performance if you're concerned about
your perform the appearance of your
performance if you make sure to work a
very serious six or seven six hours a
day or even add an hour of very serious
work on the weekend like let's say in
the morning when everybody's asleep I do
that all the
time your productivity your total
productivity your total output your GDP
gross uh domestic product of you know
you
is going to be as equal to or sometimes
even more than the average person in
your on your team unless you're not all
on a team of all high performers are
working 12 hours a day and that does
exist
so the takeaway from that is you don't
necessarily have to be busting your ass
for 8 hours a day I mean like literally
typing as fast as you can analyzing
stuff
com out with the sort of
builtin educational time any Tech worker
has into their
day not a manager on the planet that
would get mad at you for researching and
upskilling on a tech on a on a on a task
that you've been asked to do so hard
work from my
case and when you talk about it that's
how you talk about it you say I had to
do a bunch of research what is that
mean you had to spend time learning
about the thing you're in charge of
it's actually getting paid for it and
you don't feel guilty about that because
that's your job your job is to be able
to learn efficiently quickly and do the
thing just in
time
so there's a good chance that like like
me a lot of times I I'd be hard on
myself because I'm not typing as fast as
I can maximum speed you know maximum
warp the whole entire day and then I
like think about day and I was like well
what was I doing during the other you
know kind of slow
hours I was
researching I was reading about the
latest bug I was I was reading the
release notes for go I
was watching a twitch streamer about
some technology
topic seriously I'll sometimes watch
other streamers too you
know I mean like people like Head tennis
and uh
Chris Titus actually even a little bit
sometimes from
agent I I appreciate what he's doing but
I there's not a lot he says that has any
value to me so I tend to watch streamers
ala 4 I watch that stream all the
time and he's got like you know 70
people tops but the stuff he talks about
is more in line with what I need to
know
so is that you know playing or that
gooping off watching a twitch streamer
twitch you know talking about what what
they do for their job I don't think so
and it's becoming more and more normal
people are
putting TCH streamers
on in the background to keep them
company but also to kind of keep them
going while they're doing whatever
they're doing now I can't normally do
that I only do that when I'm you know
drinking coffee or eating or something
then I count as the
work so my lunchtime counts as hours at
work
right how are you real
know what I'm
saying so when I like knock off at 4:00
and everyone a lot of other people are
there until 5:30 or something plus other
people have different different
schedules a lot of people will take a
big chunk of the middle of the day out
they won't even talk about it they'll
just take a massive lunch hour or
something when at Nike people do this
all the time and it was not for the fun
they would take two hour lunch breaks
sometimes three because the the vibe the
vibe at Nike was hey we're all athletes
here we get it we need to use the
daylight and then they would a lot of
times they'd work really
late and then they'd
course
interbreed I
know Nike has a whole cultural thing
that I could talk about all day
long they really are they're inter
they're
interbred they have there's like so
many like office romance you know gossip
points to go through with them for some
reason the nature of the Beast every
time I this is why I wanted to look at
look at that smoke look at all those
charmo Burgers over there I swear if
there's one place that's going to get me
in the fall when it gets cold it's going
to be the cookout right there I cannot
pass that cookout without wanting a
burger or a hot dog or
something cuz it's just like blasting
the air with
like
amazing barbecue
smell and I have to sit here at the
light and smell it like for 10 minutes
or 5 minutes or whatever this is
it smells so good and usually by now I'm
super
hungry
yeah must resist must
resist special shakes I love I'm such a
sucker for shakes apparently so is
Steven
Seagal I've been on this completely
morbid curiosity kick looking at all the
bad Steven Seagal did and
apparently he's addicted to shakes
that's why he's like 350 lb
now he still tries to do action movies
he doesn't care he's wearing like a
triple XXL tactical
vest it's absolutely hilarious he still
thinks he's a badass it hasn't toned
down his ego at
all which is kind of an interesting
super power
oh there we go you're going to go get
one okie
dokie and no more alcohol for
me nope not even a
drop right so I'm sorry I take that back
I have my case I have to finish up cuz
I'm I hate wasting beer that's
horrible hey how how are
you it's all carbs I know look I'm not
look I'm not judging you I am not
judging you do you want to do with that
I just I don't want to just telling you
my personal
goals I just it's just I'm just too old
that shit's toxic man I know it tastes
good and it helps you socially and feel
so good uh coming home from that last
bike rid a little buzzed on that last
leg of the
bike I just unless you're going to lose
your teeth because of it like I
did I'm now convinced that that extra
beer I had is the primer the reason I
lost my teeth because I've
dodged stupid blonds on a Friday night
before in their party
cars who you know hit
me but I I didn't have my reaction time
was too
slow so
anyway milkshake I have no favorite I do
like good caramel pon
few chocolate strawberry old
good happy little
Greenway all right everybody close your
mouth don't eat any
mosquitoes we a mosquito alley
here I couldn't have made that that path
goes
straight oh
well thatth is awesome exclamation point
uh map that will show you exactly where
it's
at we're in Davidson I mean we're in
Hunter
w i just flew through a whole swarm of
bugs
remember not on the
map what did I not turn it
on it says it's
on try
again I just restarted
it oh you saw
me
no I just reset my trip for the day that
sucks but oh
well is it I know what this is it's 20
25.7 mil about you know just
under 40K I think 40
50k and now you're going to black out
you see that political
sign Democrats and Republicans come and
go but W wuang lives on
[Music]
forever he don't
wor hard to polarizing lens again too so
we get L Sun
[Applause]
Weare like 20
bucks how's the stereo is it
working I feel like this one is got to
have a little more wind noise on it this
one here left
one I'm going to check all of these
things myself when I review the stream
tonight so you don't have don't feel
like you have to say anything
but that's a nice
[Music]
here they the right
ears one of the things they added to the
action Five
camera is a second
receiver so you can do stereo now
if it gets really really really
rainy I'll probably get
it just because of
that it's even more
waterprint than it was before
don't go don't
[Music]
go I'm
oh
boy
W last h
[Music]
get the bir I'm going to move
the
um microphones
up 4 in and see if it gives you better
town
[Music]
n
sayy hi
go go go go go go
for
turn
I've never known anybody to get a
ticket but you got to be safe about
it lot of people are
not now in the suburbs most of the cars
the stop sign's optional i' I've seen at
least three cars blow through the stop
sign without even pausing to touch the G
Brake Ray Alx what a
name that say that 10 times
blind Corner left turn this is where I
actually kind of
stopped this this gu this is super
dangerous intersection people really
speed here go
she might be a last
here all the
Hallen birds are having it
out kind of bird Bight
I'm going to turn down the yoga in the
morning turn it into relaxation yoga
with some core strength
work the pro
teams there's a YouTube video of a pro
team guy that spends a week with your
pro team and they spend 30 minutes doing
Cor as soon as they wake
up for for
strength they're in
Jona
training it's a bubble mobile
h
e
all
[Music]
prob you can hear my heart with where
those speakers are like right over my
heart
damn it's so long light
I think we're after the turn sign
[Music]
kind of cool all the way down
there oh this place is dead just hopping
last night e
grab some
water $8 to have sun park your car
[Music]
going to do another lap kind of
interesting here like all the people are
in The Greenway but they don't have an
act tonight have like a band or anything
usually they have like a band or
something
[Music]
he
that's
plan anything good plan
Transformers oh wait they opened a store
up in that end spot where Mina used to
work wonder if Mina's back I doubt it I
wonder if he
back let's go
check that place CLS down I thought they
were complet closed I guess they reopen
is it a new place it is it's a new place
it's a new place yeah it's not the same
what you want hello hi people that don't
know Mina was kind of a picture on our
stream I'd stop and get a Donut coffee
there all the time we got to know her
she's learning the code
Java at
University charot
and um I'm sorry NC State in
Char yeah he's very very friendly very
nice came kind of a
fixture we haven't met that we I don't
know her name but the the waitress at
the waitress at that Daddy's there the
blonde she's really friendly she's
really nice cuz she found out we were
streaming we had we had food to Cabo
once that was
fun it's always so D traffic here is so
dangerous cuz it's just so unic
there's no signaling there's just people
doing whatever the hell they want
they're
docking you're just kind of to go with
the flow i' I've tried to pass them
before and it just doesn't go
[Music]
well feel like this guy's got something
going on
off
hey drink
boy dink
boy is that like double income no kids
w
for for
squirel
e
travel bike
w
Amazon Prime
no signal
huh for
[Music]
all
21.6 miles
okay one more left
I'm holding up
yeah said I have a heart on I decided to
go Tempo
today
so going to have
to watch
recovery tomorrow
it helps to mix it up you know
intensity and if I'm going to do that
then that means I have to turn the
intensity on yoga way down so I don't
end up blowing up
considering a weight of this bike I'm
doing pretty
good for my for
me I tell you what it
hurts definitely got some
pain America
I definitely been blowing out zone two
all the time every time there's a hill
actually been coming under two
hours I have a chance of doing that
we'll see
I just love biking so much I do love
yoga too
but I really love m game I love love I
can't do both of them at maximum
capacity because it's just too much
effort for guy my
age so if I start making the
yoga more about
recovery and core occasional core
strength situps and
stuff stretching mostly just
stretching War up the body and then just
stretch then I can then I can continue
to push it hard on my
bik which I really
love so much
fun I think the thing about cycling that
I like the most
is the sensation of speed that comes
from your own power you know that when
you you know when you're going fast you
can hear the wind kick up and everything
you know that that's because of
you and that's like a it's like a really
addictive
sensation to have that much control over
something like that right feel like a
bike just kind of amplifies your own
body power that's why don't like ebikes
I have nothing against people who use
them I just it robs you of that
sensation you get the sensation of speed
which is always good it's nice pure
adrenaline but you you lose the uh yeah
altern it right you lose the
sensation of your body being connected
to the speed
I'm probably going to write this
probably going to change the route so
these these crepe M are not on the route
anymore kind of a boring section it's
straight uphill and it's all crepe
myrtle all this up I hate
this hill hurts man it's like a long
uphill grind
that actually let me go in front of the
pub there kind of more interesting to
look
at we missed the neighborhood right
there though
that's
like what was that was like a mile and a
half 3% grade
get my legs back for the final thing
here for
beautiful evening
[Music]
oh is there a festival going on tonight
there must be this is crazy traffic for
today maybe some kind of thing going on
in Cornelius
tonight it's insane
traffic for even here
some kind of Festival going
on in
thebody know about
go check
it
[Music]
heyan check it out see what's going
on oh my God s is
popping I wonder if they got volleyball
going on in the back they have like
bikini volleyball on the
back s volleball
[Music]
I'm going to make a little
pass see what's
up man there we got to go right there a
festival like that
and when we
started I said I want to be anointed
[Music]
Goin talking about oh my
God you want to
[Music]
[Applause]
sorry you are a good deed for the
[Music]
[Applause]
day oh here you
[Music]
go good evening the part 2 202
it like
[Music]
was awesome
make
[Music]
Serv oh D that so good
should we
[Music]
get
wonder waffle
[Music]
B old BX though
oh my God is she here is should smell it
it smells so good I'm like dying cuz
it's like the end of my bike ride I'm
like totally starving right
now what's up with my camera
my camera's all screwed up I don't know
what's up
about you guys can see okay it's not
rotating for some
reason like it face locked or something
I don't even
know yeah I I think this I have to
replace this pocket 3 I have another one
but this is the one that got smash it's
okay
now yeah hopefully it'll stay okay
actually this this path goes all the way
through they made it go through it says
dead end but it's not a dead end anymore
I don't think I don't think this is a
dead end anymore I think it goes through
now let's go check it out it won't be we
could do some Adventure on our adventure
cycling like
grael bike good to see a
pixel gra
bike oh it's elementary school that's
the elementary school I I've never been
back here those are gorgeous little
houses they're so
beautiful oh they weren't kidding this
really is a dead
end the deadest of
ends but you know what I never been back
here
so there you
go such a cute little house
there I should submit my footage to
Google Street View
or my
video I want to find this the the street
that goes
through because it's really busy on the
other
Street I know there's one that does I
just don't know which one it
is no hurry
get back home and do some more moving
packing rescued a chicken down here once
I'm not even
getting it got lost it was in the cor
Road there we picked it
up set it free right here at like 12:00
at night
night he's the one he found like Rob
what are we going to do with this what
are we going to do with this chicken we
can't just leave it
well that says no outlet but this says
Smith Road Smith Drive so let's try it
is this the
one this is gorgeous down
here did I get rid of Minecraft
mode is it still Minecraft mod
try to kill
this
yeah that's always a it's always like a
moral dilemma right you help
oh we now the
Highland Elementary School okay
here look at that last
time I think this is the one that goes
through
now yeah
they take you through this neighborhood
because
it's adj the position to the country
club it's definitely not Country Club
territory they don't like it that way
they went do it anyway they had
money have different different cultural
values this is a really really ancient
Mill right here it's been
renovated that's the back of the art
center where my wife got her start again
restart right there is a studio there
used to be a a recording studio and a
all my gear to
my subw is my sound gear to a local
group at doing the studio stuff here got
a little money for it EV
but there's
antiques we're actually over by the
comic book store if you
remember I about it but we can never go
in it it's a comic book people get mad
at
you the camera they hate it
the problem with this ride is it's just
barely too long I could shave 30 minutes
off be perfect
[Music]
and by the way thank you for this
follow St yeah all right
we e
hi guys
Su super carb
baseball
night find your color children
don't talk to strangers with cameras
got
a
my cleat start
squeaking oh my God I'm
tired hour is 8 minutes we would have
been under two hours if I
had
not
detoured for
come on
H boy there was a hottie here yesterday
go look at the bot on
YouTube Whoa
We super hot Asian Prett Young
Thing bided you remember that right
pixel was like go
slower the sheo is fine she was one of
the finest people I've ever seen on a
ride and yeah I remember that sip cuz
I'm
creepy to
me all right look at you
here lots and lots of
traffic let's Morp into a
pedestrian As Americans can do of course
it turns GRE as they say that of course
it
does sure they not
turning I'm so glad you
got should we go should we go up down
the main strip the H of it should I do a
lot for you guys let me do a lot since
there's lots of people out right
now do a little
lap
hi uhoh it's a graduation photo shoot
it's got to be graduation I'm just
guessing to myself here all right
graduation photo shoot yeah yeah
absolutely
absolutely that's oh it smells like
Indian food we're behind CH Masala right
now
yeah this pretty I love my hometown this
is my hometown people can now call it my
hometown I actually live here here's the
bike here a long time now I live
here yes indeed
I like through there once it's like a
restaurant there but I don't time i' bik
through
there really CED now
down
that am way too crowed to be on the
sidewalk tonight
you're
welcome our gallery now open oo wish
been there
hi hi I'm just going really slow really
super slow I'm
sorry all
right time to go raid we are done for
the night
anybody have a raid
suggestion oh
do you guys have a raid
suggestion you know I hate doing
raiding raiding the first person pops up
looks like my Sterling
died I know not how it just
did I completely died
I just
wonder can't
right Tony Tony's a twitch con right now
but who is that Jem jam it Mac jam it
Mac okay let me go try that one
it's not letting me cancel the
r cancel rid come on come on nope it's
not let me do
it oh there we
go
J you know what I really hate the app
for rating it sucks for
rating what is it Jam of the moose
so Jamma at Mac TCH okay let's do that
it's a nice small R yeah
right I like that that's a good
one we have to wait 90 seconds
unfortunately I a streamer out of San
Francisco really
cool I like to meet you
people um what's the plan
um there is
plan tomorrow I'm going to stream yoga
but I don't know if I'm going to stream
it's it's only going to probably be 30
minutes of yoga you guys think that's
worth
streaming you guys think 30 minutes of
yoga is still worth streaming
it I don't know if it's worth
it I guess I could just to just so
people can see it or
something that's right hey yeah welcome
yeah it's the same ride every day but
the route the route's the same but the
the people and the weather changes so
what up hey
Prater I got 27 seconds left before the
raid thank you to all the new people
um uh I'm now posting my rides to
YouTube so trying to improve the quality
but if you want to like put it on while
your indoor cycling or
something also I just want to be able to
remember someone the rides that I go on
I like to go back and look we only got 6
seconds left take care everybody we'll
see you for tomorrow's
4:00 all right it's time for me to